amoeba.com 2017-02-17

# Amoeba Music - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY NOTICE**

Amoeba.com takes your privacy very seriously. Our secured socket layer (SSL) uses the latest, industry-standard 256-bit encryption technology to keep your personal information (especially your name, address and credit card number) out of the wrong hands.

Look for the "https" in the address bar of your browser when you checkout - the 's' stands for 'secure'. Our security certificate can be viewed by double-clicking the little padlock icon in the frame of your browser window.

When you make a purchase at Amoeba.com, you will be asked to provide some personal information, such as first & last name, billing address, shipping address, a contact e-mail address and telephone number. All the information we collect is primarily in the interest of accurate order processing although, if you elect to join our mailing list, we may from time to time, contact you with items of interest, or specials offers available only to our mailing list. Amoeba automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, internet cookie information, and the page you request.

Our policy does not apply when you follow links from our website to third party websites, to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that Amoeba does not employ or manage.

Amoeba does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except (i) to provide products or services you've requested, (ii) when we have your permission, (iii) when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or in connection with our establishment or exercise of our legal rights or to defend against legal claims, (iv) when we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

* * *
